<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 2</title>
      <link>/news/issue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-2/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 2 March 8th-March 14th,2020
Famous Arenznaut Moves To Olb City by Sam-Louis Alrocaet Space Boulevard-On Monday, famous Arenznaut Michael Jillerene formally moved to the ASA (Arenztopian Space Administration) location at Olb City. Mr. Jillerene is the first native Arenztopian to visit the ISS. In a nationally televised interveiw, Mr. Jillerene expressed great excitement. On Tuesday, a giant homecoming party was thrown down Space Boulevard to celebrate Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 1</title>
      <link>/news/issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-1/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 1 March 1st- March 7th, 2020
Gold Mine Found! by Tony Yuan and Clint Lee West AM District-On Tuesday, an ancient gold mine was found in the district of West AM, known to locals as West-A-Mountain district. The gold mine was discovered by Jack Peterson, a native resident, when he was volunteering to pick up trash. Says Mr. Peterson, ¨I was walking around, minding my own buisiness, when I spotted a large hole in the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorenzo A.</title>
      <link>/people/lorenzo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lorenzo/</guid>
      <description>Lorenzo A. (his full name is not shown for privacy purposes) is the king of Arenztopia. He weilds almost absolute authority. After taking power in 2020, he transformed Arenztopia into a prosperous nation. Many roads and monuments are named after him, as he is the first king. He also has a notoriously comprehensive knowledge of Greek Mythology that he constantly reminds everyone about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassie K.</title>
      <link>/people/kassie-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/kassie-k/</guid>
      <description>Kassie K. is the vice president of Arenztopia. She succeded Tony Y. in March 2020. Along with Sam K., she is the leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, specializing in Super Smash Bros Ultimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Y.</title>
      <link>/people/tony-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tony-y/</guid>
      <description>Tony Y. is the cheif designer of Arenztopia. He designed virtually everything in Arenztopia, including Arenztopia itself. The flag, capital, and palaces are all of his design. He was also formerly the vice president, and he is on a first-name basis with the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 4</title>
      <link>/news/issue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-4/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 4 March 22nd-March 28th, 2020
New Hominid Found by Tony Yuan 8700 4th Street-Workers digging the foundations of a new seiries of condos inadvertently found a new species of hominid. The new species, dubbed Australopithecus Renzosis after the king, is a 4-foot tall apelike creature that probably got here from Africa. A skull was found along with sets of ribs. ¨It´s an amazing discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire P</title>
      <link>/people/claire-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/claire-p/</guid>
      <description>Claire P. is the Royal Advisor of Arenztopia. She has served on this position for two terms. She is one of the original three people of Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James O.</title>
      <link>/people/james-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/james-o/</guid>
      <description>CAUTION! THIS PAGE IS UNDER CONSTRUCTION //////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////// James O. is a pilot for Arenztopia Airways. He holds the distinction of being the only pilot in the airline to design his own plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 3</title>
      <link>/news/issue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-3/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 3 March 15th-March 21st, 2020
Silver Growing In Crystals by Tony Yuan Albrecht Cave-Miners using enimulgemid etatetnepodag disulfate technology were able to bust the entire back and half of the side walls of Albrecht Cave. Seeing a narrow tunnel, one of the miners climbed into the tunnel. Emerging in a giant cavern, he saw silver everywhere, except these were growing in huge, diamond and quartz style crystals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History part 1</title>
      <link>/history-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history-part-1/</guid>
      <description>History part 1: The Incas In the year 1470, the great Incan emperor Pachacuti Inca Yupanqui sent a fleet of ships out from Cusco to explore new lands. The explorers, after venturing for about 500 miles out from shore, ran headfirst into a gigantic storm. It wrecked 3 of their ships and killed a dozen men, and the remaining people were forced to turn back. About a week later the brisk gale powered their crafts to a mysterious island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Information</title>
      <link>/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/info/</guid>
      <description>The Arenztopian island resides off the coast of Peru. The king is Lorenzo A, Supreme Monarch Of the Country Of Arenztopia, and he lives in Arenztopia City, which is located next to the Bay of Arenztopia at the southeast corner of the island. The 50 million people on the island enjoy a plentiful economy of $5 trillion and lots of beautiful cities. The major cities are Arenztopia City, Olb City, Noi City, Austerfeild, Arville, Shersville, New Athens, New Austin, Sitin, Shreet, New Rome, and New Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism</title>
      <link>/tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tourism/</guid>
      <description>Tourism is a major industry, and this section functions like a basic guidebook to the two biggest places in Arenztopia. Check out the guides for our two largest cities.
 Arenztopia City Olb City  Arenztopia City Arenztopia City was founded in 1565. It is a very large city with a great reputation. It contains countless fun things and a wealth of different experiences. See a map of the city center</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>