<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 1</title>
      <link>/news/issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-1/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 1 March 1st- March 7th, 2020
Gold Mine Found! by Tony Yuan and Clint Lee
West AM District-On Tuesday, an ancient gold mine was found in the district of West AM, known to locals as West-A-Mountain district. The gold mine was discovered by Jack Peterson, a native resident, when he was volunteering to pick up trash. Says Mr. Peterson, &amp;ldquo;I was walking around, minding my own buisiness, when I spotted a large hole in the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorenzo A.</title>
      <link>/people/lorenzo-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lorenzo-a/</guid>
      <description>Lorenzo A. is the creator and first president of Arenztopia. He wields lots of authority and established Modern Arenztopia in 2019. After taking power in 2020, he transformed Arenztopia into a prosperous nation. Many roads and monuments are named after him, as he is the first president. He also has a notoriously comprehensive knowledge of Greek Mythology and a degree in classics from the University of Arenztopia. He has a strong amount of influence on many things from science and tech to travel and food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 2</title>
      <link>/news/issue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-2/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 2 March 8th-March 14th,2020
Famous Arenznaut Moves To Olb City by Sam-Louis Alrocaet
Space Boulevard-On Monday, famous Arenznaut Michael Jillerene formally moved to the ASA (Arenztopian Space Administration) location at Olb City. Mr. Jillerene is the first native Arenztopian to visit the ISS. In a nationally televised interveiw, Mr. Jillerene expressed great excitement. On Tuesday, a giant homecoming party was thrown down Space Boulevard to celebrate Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Y.</title>
      <link>/people/tony-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tony-y/</guid>
      <description>Tony Yuan is the Vice President of Arenztopia. He designed the geographical layout of Arenztopia and also the flag. Tony assisted the president greatly during the COVID-19 Pandemic, and created this website and more during the pandemic. He served as Vice President from Arenztopia&#39;s creation until March 2020, when he was impeached for trying to make a peace deal with Milestopia. Kassie K. took over for him. He then won in the 2020-2021 elections and is now the Vice President again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 3</title>
      <link>/news/issue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-3/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 3
March 15th-March 21st, 2020
Silver Growing In Crystals by Tony Yuan
Albrecht Cave-Miners using enimulgemid etatetnepodag disulfate technology were able to bust the entire back and half of the side walls of Albrecht Cave. Seeing a narrow tunnel, one of the miners climbed into the tunnel. Emerging in a giant cavern, he saw silver everywhere, except these were growing in huge, diamond-and-quartz style crystals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassie K.</title>
      <link>/people/kassie-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/kassie-k/</guid>
      <description>Kassie K. is the Head Judge of Arenztopia. She formerly served as vice president; She succeded Tony Y. in March 2020 and served until December 2021, when she was succeded again by Tony Y. Along with Sam K., she is the leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, specializing in Super Smash Bros Ultimate. Her real name is Kassandra. She was also a very infulential figure in early Arenztopian politics: She was the second person to join modern Arenztopia and helped to create many things at the start including the Arenzese sign language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Arenztopia</title>
      <link>/essential_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essential_info/</guid>
      <description>Essential Information This section is your one-stop shop for information about Arenztopia. It includes all that you ever need to know about Arenztopia.
General Guide The Arenztopian Island resides off the coast of Mexico. The President is Lorenzo Avila, Ruler Of the Country Of Arenztopia, and he lives in Arenztopia City, which is located next to the Bay of Arenztopia at the southeast corner of the island. The 50 million people on the island enjoy a plentiful economy of $5 trillion and lots of beautiful cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 4</title>
      <link>/news/issue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-4/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 4 March 22nd-March 28th, 2020
New Hominid Found by Tony Yuan
8700 4th Street-Workers digging the foundations of a new seiries of condos inadvertently found a new species of hominid. The new species, dubbed Australopithecus Renzosis after the king, is a 4-foot tall apelike creature that probably got here from Africa. A skull was found along with sets of ribs. &amp;ldquo;It&#39;s an amazing discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire P.</title>
      <link>/people/claire-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/claire-p/</guid>
      <description>Claire P. is the Cheif Advisor to the president of Arenztopia. She is one of the 3 original founders of Arenztopia along with Lorenzo and Kassie. She is an influential figure in Arenztopian politics and has served for two terms as Advisor, and is now serving her third term. She was also the CEO of Dripping Cone, the largest ice cream company in the world and the largest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 5</title>
      <link>/news/issue-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-5/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 5 March 28th-April 4th
Fraud! By Tony Yuan
Natania Stadium-People in the neighboring city of Natania were shocked and appalled when an ultra-rare tree, so rare that it is only known as &amp;ldquo;K- type&amp;rdquo;, was revealed to be a common potted plant. The owner had sold it for 150 million Arenzos in an unprecedented auction that captivated thousands of eager bidders. The tree went to Nogateny Stosgat, who is an eccentric billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James O.</title>
      <link>/people/james-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/james-o/</guid>
      <description>James O. is a pilot for Arenztopia Airways. He holds the distinction of being the only pilot in the airline to design his own plane. He is also a popular and influential senator in Arenztopia. He&#39;s also a strong advocate of the Arenztopian Military and was the supreme lieutenant commander of the Royal Armed Forces of Arenztopia during the War of Chickentopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism</title>
      <link>/tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tourism/</guid>
      <description>Tourism is a major industry in Arenztopia, and this section functions like a basic guidebook to the three biggest tourist destinations in Arenztopia.
 Arenztopia City Olb City National Parks  Arenztopia City Arenztopia City was founded in 1565. It is a very large city with a great reputation. It contains countless fun things and a wealth of different experiences. See a map of the city center
Hotels Hotel De Luxe $$$ The Hotel De Luxe is the top hotel in Arenztopia City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 6</title>
      <link>/news/issue-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 05:43:46 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-6/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 6 April 5th-April 11th, 2020
Crazy! by Tony Yuan
Merdwif Mental Hospital-A man was analyzed by police and psycologists and deemed to have lost all reason as a result of intensive total self-isolation. The man, who is known by the name Steve Jobink, was reported to a mental hospital, the police, and a psychologist after he started to &amp;ldquo;yell and pull his hair out&amp;rdquo;, according to his wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livia M.</title>
      <link>/people/livia-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/livia-m/</guid>
      <description>Livia M. is a prolific entreprenuer and runs a chocolate-manufacturing empire. She is the cheif chocolate supplier for Dripping Cone, the biggest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 7</title>
      <link>/news/issue-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-7/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 7 September 20-September 26, 2020
 THE OLB CITY ANNOUNCER IS OFFICIALLY BACK IN BUISINESS! We temporarily shut down in April because one of our lead reporters caught COVID-19 and spread it to some other staff. We mourn the loss of Jake Deshinizin, who was our Chief of Printing.
 Giant Meteor Seen Over Olb City by Tony Yuan
Lower West Quarter-A huge meteor, dubbed HIO-20201862DDES, was seen streaking through the air in the evening on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living in Arenztopia</title>
      <link>/living/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/living/</guid>
      <description>Arenztopia is a vibrant country, with a plentiful economy and lots of people. In this section of the website you will learn everything you need to know about living in Arenztopia.
Housing In Arenztopia, you can find a wide array of diverse homes and apartments. Here are some of the best.
AZC Deluxe Apartments ($$) is an apartment complex in the vibrant suburban parts of Arenztopia City with a modern vibe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam K</title>
      <link>/people/sam-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sam-k/</guid>
      <description>Sam K. is a leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, along with Kassie K. He specializes in Super Mario Maker, Super Smash Bros, Super Smash Bros Ultimate, and the Pokémon trading card game. In fact, he owns a large Pokémon buiseness that operates multiple stores across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte H.</title>
      <link>/people/charlotte-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/charlotte-h/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte recently won her second term as senator and is also a taste tester for Dripping Cone ice cream company, which was voted &amp;ldquo;Best job in Arenztopia&amp;rdquo; by The Arenztopia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 8</title>
      <link>/news/issue-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-8/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 8
September 27th-October 3rd, 2020
Lost City Found by Tony Yuan
Foginhaus Lake-A major scientific discovery was made on Monday when a construction crew building a new resort on the shores of Foginhaus Lake discovered an ancient Incan city. The city was encased in 15 feet of volcanic ash when Sefifad Hill, a now-extinct volcano near the site, erupted sometime around 1483. Experts predict that the ancient metropolis extends for more than a mile inland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Information</title>
      <link>/disclaimers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/disclaimers/</guid>
      <description>Names given except for mine (Tony) are not complete for security reasons. Typos and/or faults are me and Lorenzo&#39;s complete responsibility. All mentioned events are scientifically possible and extensive research has been done to confirm that real people mentioned were alive in that time period. Most people are real, but most places are not. Portions of this website can be reproduced, stored in a retrival system, or transmitted in any form or by any means, mechanical, electronic, recording, or otherwise, but certain sections may require express permission from the Government of Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clint L.</title>
      <link>/people/clint-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/clint-l/</guid>
      <description>Clint L. is the manager of TC News and leader of a non-recognized, disputed group of islands off the coast of Arenztopia called Heruka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 9</title>
      <link>/news/issue-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-9/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 9
October 4-October 10, 2020
Explosion occurs on Sanson Tower&#39;s top floor by Tony Yuan
Sanson Tower-On Monday, a large explosion occured on the Sanson Tower&#39;s 96th floor, injuring two people, and raining glass and metal onto Sanson Plaza down below. Some of the debris also injured 3 people total on the 76th, 44th, and 21st floors. Three other people were injured in the plaza, making for a total injury count of 6 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellidy J.</title>
      <link>/people/ellidy-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ellidy-j/</guid>
      <description>Ellidy is a student currently studying theater at the University of Arenztopia. She is a distinguished Arenztopian for her contributions to the archives of the Department of Theater at Arenztopia University. She is currently serving her first term as Mayor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 10</title>
      <link>/news/issue-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-10/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 10
October 11-October 17, 2020
Factory Explodes In Olb City Outskirts by Tony Yuan
West Lane Textile Factory-On Friday, a textile factory operated by the company West Lane exploded in the industrial area in the outskirts of Olb City. Five people were killed and twenty people were injured. The factory was a historically designated building built in 1922 out of brick for the oil baron Sandon Donnasen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ishaan P.</title>
      <link>/people/ishaan-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ishaan-p/</guid>
      <description>Ishaan is a student studying archaeology at the University of Arenztopia. He discovered the important hominid called Australopithecus Renzosis, which was the first hominid ever discovered in Arenztopia. Ishaan has also recently started a successful Lego business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 11</title>
      <link>/news/issue-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-11/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 1
October 18-October 24, 2020
NOTE: This is the first issue of Volume 2 of the Olb City Announcer. Olb City Manager of Health Arrested by Tony Yuan
City Hall-Servan Wayazoya, the Manager of Health in Olb City, was arrested and fired on Tuesday on multiple counts of tax evasion, shoplifting, and misinformation. He went on trial on Wednesday, and was found guilty of evading taxes for the entire year of 2018, shoplifting a local Walmart twice in 1998 and stealing over 1,500 Arenzos worth of goods, and spreading coronavirus conspiracy theories on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 12</title>
      <link>/news/issue-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-12/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 2
October 25-October 31, 2020
 Our Halloween Raffle! We are having a Halloween raffle! Take a screenshot of this page and email it to raffles@olbcityannouncer.com with the subject &amp;ldquo;Halloween raffle&amp;rdquo; to win a pumpkin, official OCA merchandise, an orange Macbook laptop, or a Dodge Charger in an orange-and-black color scheme. Entries are accepted until November 3rd. Limit 1 entry per person. Scroll down to keep on reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suhan L.</title>
      <link>/people/suhan-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/suhan-l/</guid>
      <description>Suhan L. is originally of Chinese heritage. He joined Arenztopia and was the former Prime Minister of Arenztopia until the Prime Minister position was removed. He then made criminal deals with the terrorist organization Milestopia and was ejected from Arenztopia and thrown in jail. Recently he promised to become a beneficial citizen of Arenztopia so he was readmitted, but after his readmission he made a series of mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry P.</title>
      <link>/people/henry-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/henry-p/</guid>
      <description>Henry is an animal expert who specializes in corgies. He has saved over 100,000 animals in Arenztopia as of September 2020 from his goverment funded buisiness &amp;ldquo;Arenztopia Animals&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 13</title>
      <link>/news/issue-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-13/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 3 November 1-November 7, 2020
Arenztopian Elections Kickoff by Tony Yuan
On Monday, the 2020-2021 Arenztopian Elections were kicked off; many campaign signs have already benn spotted all over Arenztopia. Tony Yuan (S) and Ellidy J. (E) are both competing against incumbent Kassie K. (R) for the Vice President position. James O. announced on Friday that he was running for Senator. Tony Yuan and Ellidy are also both cometing for the Mayor position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan H.</title>
      <link>/people/ethan-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ethan-h/</guid>
      <description>Ethan H. is the manager of the renowned and huge chain of art stores known as Arenztopia Art Store. He is a prominent citizen and is the richest person in Austerfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 14</title>
      <link>/news/issue-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-14/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 4
November 8-November 14, 2020
APAIS-2 reaches asteroid by Tony Yuan
Derlass Space Facility-The revolutionary satellite APAIS-2 (All-Purpose Asteroid Imaging System) reached the asteroid Vesta on Tuesday after a journey of more than three years. It will orbit the asteroid for four Earth years collecting data about Vesta. This will help astronomers assess if Vesta will be suitable for a future mission. &amp;ldquo;We are eyeing the Asteroid Belt as a potential destination for intergalactic explorers after stopping at Mars, which could become a &amp;lsquo;gas station&amp;rsquo; for future missions,&amp;rdquo; the director of the APAIS team, Fred Nelson, said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowen F.</title>
      <link>/people/bowen-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/bowen-f/</guid>
      <description>Bowen F. is an influential citizen. He used to be the police chief of the Arenztopia City Police Department (ACPD) and he played an integral part in catching crime boss Miles Jordan, among many others. He is now the governor of a disputed and unrecognized state off the cosat of Arenztopia, near Clint L.&amp;lsquo;s unrecognized state of Heruka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 15</title>
      <link>/news/issue-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-15/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 5
November 15-November 21, 2020
Blackout by Tony Yuan
South Olb City Electricity Center-On Tuesday, a blackout happened that affected half a million people in South Olb City. The blackout was caused by several wires failing at South Olb City Electricity Center. Many people reported a sudden extinguishing of their lights at about 10:00 in the morning. The ISS also captured a measurement of about a third of the electricity of Olb City shutting off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 16</title>
      <link>/news/issue-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-16/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 6
November 22-November 28, 2020
Huge new oil deposit found by Tony Yuan
Sar Basin-On Wednesday, an oil platform hit upon a gigantic underground pool of oil on the north edge of the Sar Basin, a large underwater plain some 40 miles out from the coast. The oil platform, which was built in 2016 and chistened the Haruga, pumped in oil for over two hours before calling it a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael A.</title>
      <link>/people/michael-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/michael-a/</guid>
      <description>Michael A. is a newcomer to Arenztopia, but has already been elected to the position of Senator. He says that he initially entered the elections as a joke and was amazed by his own win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cort C.</title>
      <link>/people/cort-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/cort-c/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 17</title>
      <link>/news/issue-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-17/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 7 November 29-December 5, 2020
Flood by Tony Yuan
Servap Hydropower Plant-On Tuesday, a small hydropower plant failed upstream of the Tortoise River. Officials are still trying to determine the cause of the failure. Based on preliminary evidence, it seems like an object had gotten lodged into the pipe which held the turbine, and when the fast-moving turbine struck the object, the plant exploded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 18</title>
      <link>/news/issue-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-18/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 8 December 6-December 12, 2020
Famous Athlete Missing by Tony Yuan
Marifu Hills-Famous soccer player Luke Jasil went missing on Wednesday. Police say he disappeared from his home at night. Officials think that he was kidnapped. The OCPD has published five suspects on its website at ocpd.org/suspects. &amp;ldquo;This is an act of grevious cowardice,&amp;rdquo; Jack Carter, the leader of the Olb City Detective Association, said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raghav R.</title>
      <link>/people/raghav-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/raghav-r/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 19</title>
      <link>/news/issue-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-19/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 19 December 13th-December 19th, 2020
Japenese Military Bunker Found by Tony Yuan
Bull Horn Oasis-On Monday, gold miners digging in the Arenztopian Desert hit a strong and suspisciously flat rock. After 2 days of digging they found a bunker marked with the Japanese flag. Scientists and historians believe that this bunker was built during WW2 to combat the American soldiers who had used Arenztopia as a US base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Z.</title>
      <link>/people/ryan-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ryan-z/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Z. is a famous pilot for Arenztopia Airways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 20</title>
      <link>/news/issue-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-20/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 10 December 20th-December 26th, 2020
Election Results Announced by Tony Yuan
On Sunday, the results of the 2020-2021 Arenztopian Elections were announced. The position of Vice President was given to Tony Yuan, while the Mayor position was won by Ellidy J. Claire P. won a third term as Advisor, and the senators are James O., Charlotte H, and Michael A. Cheif Judge is Kassie K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sai G.</title>
      <link>/people/sai-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sai-g/</guid>
      <description>Sai G. is a private investigator for the OCPD and ACPD. She is currently investigating the unsolved mystery of the explosion at the Tortoise River Freight Port, which was mentioned in Issue 31 of the Olb City Announcer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 21</title>
      <link>/news/issue-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-21/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 1 December 27th-January 2nd, 2020 and 2021, respectively
Huge, virtual New Year&#39;s party happens by Tony Yuan
The Olb City government staged a huge New Year&#39;s celebration in Olb Plaza, with fireworks and acrobats. The show was livestreamed on Youtube but almost nobody was there in person. After the show, a couple thousand people gradually filtered into the plaza and enjoyed the beautiful veiws of the plaza covered in snow, after the snowstorm on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasneem A.</title>
      <link>/people/tasneem-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tasneem-a/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 22</title>
      <link>/news/issue-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-22/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 2 January 3rd-January 9th, 2021
Plane crashes near airport hotel By Tony Yuan
Olb City International Airport-A Boeing 727 overshot the runway at OCIA on Monday and broke apart after hitting the ground and exploding just 50 meters from the Hilton hotel at OCIA. Police say that at least 20 people have died, 50 are injured, and the rest are missing. The wreckage of the plane was quickly doused with water and investigators are now searching for clues as to what might have caused the crash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sahana R.</title>
      <link>/people/sahana-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sahana-r/</guid>
      <description>Sahana R. is a private investigator based in Olb City. She is currently working with Sai G. on the unsolved mystery of the explosion at the Tortoise River Freight Port, which was mentioned in Issue 31 of the Olb City Announcer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 23</title>
      <link>/news/issue-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-23/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 3 January 10th-January 16th, 2021
Billionare Entrepreneur Arrested By Tony Yuan
Olb City Police Department Headquarters-Billionare entrepreneur Oliver Tichiad has been arrested on five counts of money laundering and three counts of tax evasion. Mr. Tichiad is the founder of popular translation service Ottam, and his net worth is over 12 billion dollars.
Oliver Tichiad&#39;s official portrait at ottam.com
Tichiad is due to go on trial Tuesday next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 24</title>
      <link>/news/issue-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-24/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 4 January 17th-January 23rd, 2021
Ship Collision in Arenztopia Bay By Tony Yuan
Arenztopia Bay-A freighter collided with another freighter in Arenztopia Bay on Tuesday. Over 300 containers were lost and 12 injuries were reported, with 10 deaths reported so far. The control center at Arenztopia Bay issued a detailed report several hours after the crash, which says that the freighter Marice steamed into the bay, and collided with the side of the freighter Albatross, which was heading out of the bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 25</title>
      <link>/news/issue-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-25/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 5 January 24th-January 30th, 2021
Fatal Car Crash By Tony Yuan
AR-10-On Tuesday, a fatal car crash occured on AR-10, which involved two semi trucks and a sedan, and killed 3 people. According to footage, one of the semi trucks seems to have accidentally swerved into the wrong lane, but when the driver realized the mistake, he tried to swerve into the lane that he was in before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 26</title>
      <link>/news/issue-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-26/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 6 January 31st-February 6th, 2021
Mysterious new movie being filmed By Tony Yuan
Natania City-Reports say that a mysterious new movie is being filmed in Natania City. When our reporters tried to visit the set, they were turned away. This movie has been shrouded in mystery since rumors got out of its development in July. There is almost nothing known about it, although most people agree that it is being produced by Naigon and Sons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 27</title>
      <link>/news/issue-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-27/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 7 February 7th-February 13th, 2021
Huge New Building Complex Planned By Tony Yuan
North Olb City-A new and ambitious building complex was announced in the trending neighborhood of Riverpark Heights. It is going to be designed, built, and sold by prestigious realty firm McMilleryége &amp;amp; Sons. The complex will feature eight modern buildings designed to be green and almost entirely self-sufficient, and it will have over 1 and a half million square feet of space spread out over a lot of 8 acres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 28</title>
      <link>/news/issue-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-28/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 8 February 14th-February 20th, 2021
Semi Truck Slams Into Building By Tony Yuan
Downtown Olb City-A semi truck went out of control and slammed into the Wharton Park office building on ice-covered roads on 1st Street Monday. Thirteen people have died and a further twenty are in the hospital. According to security camera footage, the truck swerved around crazily before crashing violently into the office building, where it promptly exploded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 29</title>
      <link>/news/issue-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-29/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 9 February 21st-February 27th, 2021
Nogateny Stosgat loses 38 billion Arenzos By Tony Yuan
Arenztopian Stock Market-Famous billionare Nogateny Stosgat (See Issue 5) lost almost 38 billion Arenzos overnight as two of his companies, TechDaily Magazine and Stosgat Industries, experienced a stock drop of over 100 billion Arenzos on Tuesday. The 38 billion Arenzos are a huge chunk of Mr. Stosgat&#39;s 90 billion Arenzo fortune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 30</title>
      <link>/news/issue-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-30/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 3, Issue 10 February 28th-March 6th, 2021
 CELEBRATING ONE YEAR OF THE OLB CITY ANNOUNCER! This week, we are celebrating one year of the Olb City Announcer: Our first issue was for the week of March 1 to March 7th, 2020. However, this one-year anniversary is including a several-month hiatus in the summer of 2020 due to a COVID-19 outbreak in our offices.  Az Scoops Sued for 180 million Arenzos By Lorenzo Avila and Tony Yuan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 31</title>
      <link>/news/issue-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-31/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 1 March 7th-March 13th, 2021
 SPECIAL FEATURE: ONE YEAR OF COVID For this issue, we are going to be publishing many COVID-related articles to commemorate the one year anniversary of the WHO&#39;s pandemic declaration on March 11th.  Explosion at Cargo Port By Tony Yuan
Tortoise River Freight Port-A huge explosion rocked the Tortoise River Freight Port on Tuesday. The Tortoise River Freight Port is a major port on the Tortoise River about 30 miles downstream from Olb City, at a place where the Tortoise River expands to 1000 feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 32</title>
      <link>/news/issue-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-32/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 2 March 14th-March 20th, 2021
New Transportation Plan Announced By Tony Yuan
Olb City Department of Transportation-A new transportation expansion bill was announced on Monday. If passed, it will feature three new lines for the subway network, light rail service straight to and from Arenztopia Mountain National Park, a &amp;ldquo;light rail overpass&amp;rdquo; network, and more. The first new subway line will run from Olb Plaza to Olb University, with stops at Villa Palenque, the Anda-Tortoise Junction, City Hall, and GD &amp;amp; Co HQ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 33</title>
      <link>/news/issue-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-33/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 3 March 21st-March 27th, 2021
New Airport Planned By Tony Yuan
Hallington-City officials have voted to plan and design a new, second airport near the small satellite town of Hallington. The airport will be called the Hallington-Olb City International Airport (HOCIA), and it will house over 800 restaraunts and shops, with ten 9,000 meter runways and over 300 gates. The airport will have four terminals, each with an estimated 500,000 square feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 34</title>
      <link>/news/issue-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-34/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 4 March 28th-April 3rd, 2021
Huge New Building Announced By Tony Yuan
Downtown Olb City-The engineering and architecture firm S. F. Grosby &amp;amp; Co. announced the building of a gigantic new skyscraper, which will cover an entire block and rise 101 stories into the sky. It will be situated on the shore of Lake Ferguson. The tower&#39;s working name is the Sky101 Tower and it will be the tallest tower in Olb City upon its completion in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 35</title>
      <link>/news/issue-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-35/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 5 April 4th-April 10th, 2021
New Territory Annexed By Lorenzo Avila and Tony Yuan
Choran City-A small country off the coast of Chile called the Republic of Modinau was annexed into Arenztopia on Tuesday, after money problems caused them to ask for annexation. The Republic of Modinau has now become the Modinau Region, and it has added two new large cities to Arenztopia: Choran City, their former capital, and Salnez, a large fishing town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 36</title>
      <link>/news/issue-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-36/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 6 April 11th-April 17th, 2021
Woodchuck Criminals Caught By Tony Yuan
Olb City Courthouse-On Monday, police caught the infamous Woodchuck Criminals while they were robbing a bank in Olb City. The Woodchuck Criminals murdered three people in the space of a year, and a jury sentenced them to life in jail. The details of who they are are a bit shadowy, however we have a tentative identification of John Kanhson, Tom McBluecal, and Harry Rasdin, along with Chris Owens, who was caught last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 37</title>
      <link>/news/issue-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-37/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 7
April 18th-April 24th, 2021
Luke Jasil Kidnapping Mystery Solved! By Tony Yuan
8930 Wensal Lane-Private investigator Sai G. has solved the long-standing mystery of the presumed kidnapping of famous soccer player Luke Jasil. The culprit was determined to be 59 year old Frederick Winston. According to the OCPD, Winston was illegally smuggling wine and alcohol by hiding it in Pringles cans. Winston was also convicted of stealing caviar from multiple luxury stores and also hiding it in Pringles cans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 38</title>
      <link>/news/issue-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-38/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 8
April 25th-May 1st, 2021
Technology Startup Releases New Phone By Tony Yuan
6220 Main Street-On Tuesday, the Arenztopian technology startup Jupiter announced their first phone, the Jupiter III. The phone will be powered by Jupiter&#39;s own chip, the R1 Dominator, and it will have over 25 GB of storage. The III will run Jupiter&#39;s own operating system, CarbonOS, and it will be compatible with Jupiter&#39;s other devices, the Jupiter I laptop and the Jupiter II laptop, along with the JupiterWatch and JupiterPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 39</title>
      <link>/news/issue-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-39/</guid>
      <description>CAUTION!!! THIS PAGE IS STILL BEING WORKED ON PROCEED AT YOUR OWN RISK  The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 9
May 2nd-May 8th, 2021
Huge Lawsuit Filed By Lorenzo Avila and Tony Yuan
Olb City Courthouse-On Monday, Demial Kondo filed a lawsuit against his partner Bedli Amat. Both are millionaires and jointly own the massive company KandaRestauraunts Holdings Company, Inc. which has a net worth of 100 billion dollars and owns such chains like Jamaisvu, the famous fine dining store, and large stakes in McDonalds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 40</title>
      <link>/news/issue-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-40/</guid>
      <description>CAUTION!!! THIS PAGE IS STILL BEING WORKED ON PROCEED AT YOUR OWN RISK  The Olb City Announcer Volume 4, Issue 10
May 9th-May 15th, 2021
Cover Story By Lorenzo Avila and Tony Yuan
Arts by Owen Miyazoi
The Sculptor&#39;s Association of Arenztopia (SAA) announced its dissolution on Thursday, after a scandal which caused the resignment of prominent artists like Bao Mokino, Moe Kinakshi, Miekl Kyonankii, and others. The CEO of the association, a classical-style artist named Sinclair Yindranishikan, was found to be a member of the Classicist Revolutionaries, which attacked Miekl Kyonankii&#39;s studio a couple months ago (See Issue 24).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 41</title>
      <link>/news/issue-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-41/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 5, Issue 1
May 16th-May 22nd, 2021
Underwater City Planned By Lorenzo Avila and Tony Yuan
Arenztopia City-The contractor company Alsburg Contractors is announcing a massive and ambitious underwater city called Verre D&#39;eau. The city has been designed to minimize impact on the surrounding wildlife. It will feature 13 pressurized domes spead out over the seafloor, and each dome will be 100 feet tall, have two layers, be held up by metal trusses, and be made from 1-inch thick sheets of Plexiglass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 42</title>
      <link>/news/issue-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-42/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 5, Issue 2
May 23rd-May 29th, 2021
Cover Story By Tony Yuan
Arts by Owen Miyazoi
Sports By Sam-Louis Alrocaet
The first and second races of the ASCRO stock car racing tournament happened on Tuesday and Wednesday. Driver Chuck Garrotte in car #49 won the first race, which was held at Canopia Speedway. Driver Lars McKaulsen in car #101 won the second race, which was held at the NACircuit in New Austin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/people/krisha-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/krisha-p/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>