<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 1</title>
      <link>/news/issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-1/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 1 March 1st- March 7th, 2020
Gold Mine Found! by Tony Yuan and Clint Lee
West AM District-On Tuesday, an ancient gold mine was found in the district of West AM, known to locals as West-A-Mountain district. The gold mine was discovered by Jack Peterson, a native resident, when he was volunteering to pick up trash. Says Mr. Peterson, ¨I was walking around, minding my own buisiness, when I spotted a large hole in the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila</title>
      <link>/people/lorenzo-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lorenzo-a/</guid>
      <description>Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila is the king of Arenztopia. He wields lots of authority. After taking power in 2020, he transformed Arenztopia into a prosperous nation. Many roads and monuments are named after him, as he is the first king. He also has a notoriously comprehensive knowledge of Greek Mythology that he constantly reminds everyone about. His full title is Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila the First, Supreme Monarch of the Country of Arenztopia, Wielder of Great Power, Supreme and Unobstructed Admiral-Lieutenant General of the Royal Armed Forces of the Country of Arenztopia, Lord-Mayor of Arenztopia City, Order of the Royal Suite of Arenztopia, Knight of the Province of Umivrw, Honorary Fellow of the Coastal Region of the Country of Arenztopia, Knower of Greek Myth, Reader of All Books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 2</title>
      <link>/news/issue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-2/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 2 March 8th-March 14th,2020
Famous Arenznaut Moves To Olb City by Sam-Louis Alrocaet
Space Boulevard-On Monday, famous Arenznaut Michael Jillerene formally moved to the ASA (Arenztopian Space Administration) location at Olb City. Mr. Jillerene is the first native Arenztopian to visit the ISS. In a nationally televised interveiw, Mr. Jillerene expressed great excitement. On Tuesday, a giant homecoming party was thrown down Space Boulevard to celebrate Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassie K.</title>
      <link>/people/kassie-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/kassie-k/</guid>
      <description>Kassie K. is the vice president of Arenztopia. Her real name is Kassandra. She succeded Tony Y. in March 2020. Along with Sam K., she is the leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, specializing in Super Smash Bros Ultimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 3</title>
      <link>/news/issue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-3/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 3
March 15th-March 21st, 2020
Silver Growing In Crystals by Tony Yuan
Albrecht Cave-Miners using enimulgemid etatetnepodag disulfate technology were able to bust the entire back and half of the side walls of Albrecht Cave. Seeing a narrow tunnel, one of the miners climbed into the tunnel. Emerging in a giant cavern, he saw silver everywhere, except these were growing in huge, diamond and quartz style crystals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Information</title>
      <link>/general_info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/general_info/</guid>
      <description>General Information The Arenztopian island resides off the coast of Mexico. The king is Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila, Supreme Monarch Of the Country Of Arenztopia, and he lives in Arenztopia City, which is located next to the Bay of Arenztopia at the southeast corner of the island. The 50 million people on the island enjoy a plentiful economy of $5 trillion and lots of beautiful cities. The major cities are Arenztopia City, Olb City, Noi City, Austerfeild, Arville, Shersville, New Athens, New Austin, Sitin, Shreet, New Rome, and New Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Y.</title>
      <link>/people/tony-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tony-y/</guid>
      <description>Tony Y. is the chief designer of Arenztopia. He designed virtually everything in Arenztopia, including Arenztopia itself. The flag, capital, and palaces are all of his design. He was also formerly the vice president, and he is on a first-name basis with the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 4</title>
      <link>/news/issue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-4/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 4 March 22nd-March 28th, 2020
New Hominid Found by Tony Yuan
8700 4th Street-Workers digging the foundations of a new seiries of condos inadvertently found a new species of hominid. The new species, dubbed Australopithecus Renzosis after the king, is a 4-foot tall apelike creature that probably got here from Africa. A skull was found along with sets of ribs. ¨It´s an amazing discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/history/</guid>
      <description>History part 1: The Incas In the year 1470, the great Incan emperor Pachacuti Inca Yupanqui sent a fleet of ships out from Cusco to explore new lands. The explorers, after venturing for about 500 miles out from shore, ran headfirst into a gigantic storm. It wrecked 3 of their ships and killed a dozen men, and the remaining people were forced to turn back. About a week later the brisk gale powered their crafts to a mysterious island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire P.</title>
      <link>/people/claire-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/claire-p/</guid>
      <description>Claire P. is the Royal Advisor of Arenztopia. She has served on this position for two terms. Claire is also a noted journalist. She is one of the original three people of Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 5</title>
      <link>/news/issue-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-5/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 5 March 28th-April 4th
Fraud! By Tony Yuan
Natania Stadium-People in the neigjboring city of Natania were shocked and appalled when an ultra-rare tree, so rare that it is only known as ¨K- type¨, was revealed to be a common potted plant. The owner had sold it for 150 million Arenzos in an unprecedented auction that captivated thousands of eager bidders. The tree went to Nogateny Stosgat, who is an eccentric billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James O.</title>
      <link>/people/james-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/james-o/</guid>
      <description>James O. is a pilot for Arenztopia Airways. He holds the distinction of being the only pilot in the airline to design his own plane. He is also a popular and influential senator in Arenztopia. He&#39;s also a strong advocate of the Arenztopian Military and was the supreme lieutenant commander of the Royal Armed Forces of Arenztopia during the War of Chickentopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism</title>
      <link>/tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tourism/</guid>
      <description>Tourism is a major industry in Arenztopia, and this section functions like a basic guidebook to the two biggest places in Arenztopia. Check out the guides for our two largest cities.
 Arenztopia City Olb City National Parks  Arenztopia City Arenztopia City was founded in 1565. It is a very large city with a great reputation. It contains countless fun things and a wealth of different experiences. See a map of the city center</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 6</title>
      <link>/news/issue-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 05:43:46 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-6/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 6 April 5th-April 11th, 2020
Crazy! by Tony Yuan
Merdwif Mental Hospital-A man was analyzed by police and psycologists and deemed to have lost all reason as a result of intensive total self-isolation. The man, who is known by the name Steve Jobink, was reported to a mental hospital, the police, and a psychologist after he started to &amp;ldquo;yell and pull his hair out&amp;rdquo;, according to his wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livia M.</title>
      <link>/people/livia-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/livia-m/</guid>
      <description>Livia M. is a prolific entreprenuer and runs a chocolate-manufacturing empire. She is the cheif chocolate supplier for Dripping Cone, the biggest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam K</title>
      <link>/people/sam-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sam-k/</guid>
      <description>Sam K. is a leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, along with Kassie K. He specializes in Super Mario Maker, Super Smash Bros, Super Smash Bros Ultimate, and the Pokémon trading card game. In fact, he owns a large Pokémon buiseness that operates multiple stores across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 7</title>
      <link>/news/issue-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-7/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 7 September 20-September 26, 2020
 THE OLB CITY ANNOUNCER IS OFFICIALLY BACK IN BUISINESS! We temporarily shut down in April because one of our lead reporters caught COVID-19 and spread it to some other staff. We mourn the loss of Jake Deshinizin, who was our Chief of Printing.
 Giant Meteor Seen Over Olb City by Tony Yuan
Lower West Quarter-A huge meteor, dubbed HIO-20201862DDES, was seen streaking through the air in the evening on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte H.</title>
      <link>/people/charlotte-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/charlotte-h/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte is a senator and also a taste tester for Dripping Cone ice cream company, which was voted &amp;ldquo;Best job in Arenztopia&amp;rdquo; by The Arenztopia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimers and Acknowledgments</title>
      <link>/disclaimers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/disclaimers/</guid>
      <description>Names given except for my own are not complete for security reasons. Typos and/or faults are my complete responsibility. All mentioned events are scientifically possible and extensive research has been done to confirm that real people mentioned were alive in that time period. Most people are real, but some places are not. Portions of this website can be reproduced, stored in a retrival system, or transmitted in any form or by any means, mechanical, electronic, recording, or otherwise, but certain sections may require express permission from the Government of Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clint L.</title>
      <link>/people/clint-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/clint-l/</guid>
      <description>Clint L. is the manager of TC News and leader of a non-recognized, disputed group of islands off the coast of Arenztopia called Heruka. His country is in a disputed state of war with Arenztopia. The dispute is recognized by Clint and to a certain extent by Lorenzo but is not recognized by any other influential Arenztopians and neither side has taken major military or diplomatic or war-related actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 8</title>
      <link>/news/issue-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-8/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 8
September 27th-October 3rd, 2020
Lost City Found by Tony Yuan
Foginhaus Lake-A major scientific discovery was made on Monday when a construction crew building a new resort on the shores of Foginhaus Lake discovered an ancient Incan city. The city was encased in 15 feet of volcanic ash when Sefifad Hill, a now-extinct volcano near the site, erupted sometime around 1483. Experts predict that the ancient metropolis extends for more than a mile inland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellidy J.</title>
      <link>/people/ellidy-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ellidy-j/</guid>
      <description>Ellidy is a student currently studying theater at the University of Arenztopia. She is a distinguished Arenztopian for her contributions to the archives of the Department of Theater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 9</title>
      <link>/news/issue-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-9/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 9
October 4-October {11/10 &amp;lt;- Notes: decide on this}, 2020
Explosion occurs on Sanson Tower&#39;s top floor by Tony Yuan
Sanson Tower-On Monday, a large explosion occured on the Sanson Tower&#39;s 96th floor, injuring two people, and raining glass and metal onto Sanson Plaza down below. Some of the debris also injured 3 people total on the 76th, 44th, and 21st floors. One person was injured in the plaza, making for a total injury count of 6 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ishaan P.</title>
      <link>/people/ishaan-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ishaan-p/</guid>
      <description>Ishaan is a student studying archaeology at the University of Arenztopia. He discovered the important hominid called Australopithecus Renzosis, which was the first hominid ever discovered in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suhan L.</title>
      <link>/people/suhan-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/suhan-l/</guid>
      <description>Suhan Li is a conflicted figure in Arenztopian politics, having served as the first and only Prime Minister of Arenztopia from the middle of January 2020 until the removal of the Prime Minister post in the middle of March 2020. After he was forced to resign, he threatened to bomb Arenztopia, so he was put in jail. However, less than a week later he broke out when an enemy helicopter airlifted him out of the prison.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry P.</title>
      <link>/people/henry-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/henry-p/</guid>
      <description>Henry is an animal expert who specializes in corgys. He has saved over 100,000 animals in Arenztopia as of September 2020 from his goverment funded buisiness &amp;ldquo;Arenztopia Animals&amp;rdquo; featured in Olb City Announcer Issue 7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan H.</title>
      <link>/people/ethan-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ethan-h/</guid>
      <description>Ethan H. is the manager of the renowned and huge chain of art stores known as Arenztopia Art Store. He is a prominent citizen, often coming to government meetings, and is the richest person in Austerfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowen F.</title>
      <link>/people/bowen-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/bowen-f/</guid>
      <description>Bowen F. is an influential citizen. He is the police chief of the Arenztopia City Police Department (ACPD), and he played an integral part in catching the Woodchuck criminals, crime boss Miles Jordan, and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Olb City Announcer Special Edition: September 23</title>
      <link>/news/special-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/special-edition/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer: SPECIAL EDITION Volume 1, Issue 7 and 1/2 September 23
BREAKING NEWS REPORT! Arenztopia Mountain is the home to a top security prison, but 2 robbers have broken out. They are alive and are hunting down targets. A few people have been put under witness protection. One, named Bob Richy, commented &amp;ldquo;I am not scared for me, I am scared for my family.&amp;rdquo; Top detectives are on the case.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>