<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 1</title>
      <link>/news/issue-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-1/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 1 March 1st- March 7th, 2020
Gold Mine Found! by Tony Yuan and Clint Lee
West AM District-On Tuesday, an ancient gold mine was found in the district of West AM, known to locals as West-A-Mountain district. The gold mine was discovered by Jack Peterson, a native resident, when he was volunteering to pick up trash. Says Mr. Peterson, ¨I was walking around, minding my own buisiness, when I spotted a large hole in the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 2</title>
      <link>/news/issue-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-2/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 2 March 8th-March 14th,2020
Famous Arenznaut Moves To Olb City by Sam-Louis Alrocaet
Space Boulevard-On Monday, famous Arenznaut Michael Jillerene formally moved to the ASA (Arenztopian Space Administration) location at Olb City. Mr. Jillerene is the first native Arenztopian to visit the ISS. In a nationally televised interveiw, Mr. Jillerene expressed great excitement. On Tuesday, a giant homecoming party was thrown down Space Boulevard to celebrate Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 3</title>
      <link>/news/issue-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-3/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 3
March 15th-March 21st, 2020
Silver Growing In Crystals by Tony Yuan
Albrecht Cave-Miners using enimulgemid etatetnepodag disulfate technology were able to bust the entire back and half of the side walls of Albrecht Cave. Seeing a narrow tunnel, one of the miners climbed into the tunnel. Emerging in a giant cavern, he saw silver everywhere, except these were growing in huge, diamond and quartz style crystals!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 4</title>
      <link>/news/issue-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-4/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 4 March 22nd-March 28th, 2020
New Hominid Found by Tony Yuan
8700 4th Street-Workers digging the foundations of a new seiries of condos inadvertently found a new species of hominid. The new species, dubbed Australopithecus Renzosis after the king, is a 4-foot tall apelike creature that probably got here from Africa. A skull was found along with sets of ribs. ¨It´s an amazing discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 5</title>
      <link>/news/issue-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-5/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 5 March 28th-April 4th
Fraud! By Tony Yuan
Natania Stadium-People in the neigjboring city of Natania were shocked and appalled when an ultra-rare tree, so rare that it is only known as ¨K- type¨, was revealed to be a common potted plant. The owner had sold it for 150 million Arenzos in an unprecedented auction that captivated thousands of eager bidders. The tree went to Nogateny Stosgat, who is an eccentric billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 6</title>
      <link>/news/issue-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 05:43:46 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-6/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 6 April 5th-April 11th, 2020
Crazy! by Tony Yuan
Merdwif Mental Hospital-A man was analyzed by police and psycologists and deemed to have lost all reason as a result of intensive total self-isolation. The man, who is known by the name Steve Jobink, was reported to a mental hospital, the police, and a psychologist after he started to &amp;ldquo;yell and pull his hair out&amp;rdquo;, according to his wife.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 7</title>
      <link>/news/issue-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 01:22:56 +1900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-7/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 7 September 20-September 26, 2020
 THE OLB CITY ANNOUNCER IS OFFICIALLY BACK IN BUISINESS! We temporarily shut down in April because one of our lead reporters caught COVID-19 and spread it to some other staff. We mourn the loss of Jake Deshinizin, who was our Chief of Printing.
 Giant Meteor Seen Over Olb City by Tony Yuan
Lower West Quarter-A huge meteor, dubbed HIO-20201862DDES, was seen streaking through the air in the evening on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 8</title>
      <link>/news/issue-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-8/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 8
September 27th-October 3rd, 2020
Lost City Found by Tony Yuan
Foginhaus Lake-A major scientific discovery was made on Monday when a construction crew building a new resort on the shores of Foginhaus Lake discovered an ancient Incan city. The city was encased in 15 feet of volcanic ash when Sefifad Hill, a now-extinct volcano near the site, erupted sometime around 1483. Experts predict that the ancient metropolis extends for more than a mile inland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 9</title>
      <link>/news/issue-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-9/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 9
October 4-October 10, 2020
Explosion occurs on Sanson Tower&#39;s top floor by Tony Yuan
Sanson Tower-On Monday, a large explosion occured on the Sanson Tower&#39;s 96th floor, injuring two people, and raining glass and metal onto Sanson Plaza down below. Some of the debris also injured 3 people total on the 76th, 44th, and 21st floors. One person was injured in the plaza, making for a total injury count of 6 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 10</title>
      <link>/news/issue-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-10/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 10
October 11-October 17, 2020
Factory Explodes In Olb City Outskirts by Tony Yuan
West Lane Textile Factory-On Friday, a textile factory operated by the company West Lane exploded in the industrial area in the outskirts of Olb City. Five people were killed and twenty people were injured. The factory was a historically designated building built in 1922 out of brick for the oil baron Sandon Donnasen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 11</title>
      <link>/news/issue-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-11/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 2, Issue 1
October 18-October 24, 2020
NOTE: This is the first issue of Volume 2 of the Olb City Announcer. Olb City Manager of Health Arrested by Tony Yuan
City Hall-Servan Wayazoya, the Manager of Health in Olb City, was arrested and fired on Tuesday on multiple counts of tax evasion, shoplifting, and misinformation. He went on trial on Wednesday, and was found guilty of evading taxes for the entire year of 2018, shoplifting a local Walmart twice in 1998 and stealing over 1,500 Arenzos worth of goods, and spreading coronavirus conspiracy theories on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 12</title>
      <link>/news/issue-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-12/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 12
October 25-October 31, 2020
 Our Halloween Raffle! We are having a Halloween raffle! Take a screenshot of this page and email it to raffles@olbcityannouncer.com with the subject &amp;ldquo;Halloween raffle&amp;rdquo; to win a pumpkin, official OCA merchandise, an orange Macbook laptop, or a Dodge Charger in an orange-and-black color scheme. Entries are accepted until November 3rd. Limit 1 entry per person. Scroll down to keep on reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 13</title>
      <link>/news/issue-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-13/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 13 November 1-November 7, 2020
Arenztopian Elections Kickoff by Tony Yuan
On Monday, the 2020-2021 Arenztopian Elections were kicked off; many campaign signs have already benn spotted all over Arenztopia. Tony Yuan (S) and Ellidy J. (E) are both competing against incumbent Kassie K. (R) for the Vice President position. James O. announced on Friday that he was running for Senator. Tony Yuan and Ellidy are also both cometing for the Mayor position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issue 14</title>
      <link>/news/issue-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-14/</guid>
      <description>The Olb City Announcer Volume 1, Issue 12
November 8-November 14, 2020
APAIS-2 reaches asteroid by Tony Yuan
Derlass Space Facility-The revolutionary satellite APAIS-2 (All-Purpose Asteroid Imaging System) reached the asteroid Vesta on Tuesday after a journey of more than three years. It will orbit the asteroid for four Earth years collecting data about Vesta. This will help astronomers assess if Vesta will be suitable for a future mission. &amp;ldquo;We are eyeing the Asteroid Belt as a potential destination for intergalactic explorers after stopping at Mars, which could become a &amp;lsquo;gas station&amp;rsquo; for future missions,&amp;rdquo; the Arenztopian Officer of Science, Tony Yuan, said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/news/issue-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-15/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/news/issue-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/issue-16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>