<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila</title>
      <link>/people/lorenzo-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lorenzo-a/</guid>
      <description>Lorenzo Sebastian Javier Avila is the creator and first president of Arenztopia. He wields lots of authority and established Modern Arenztopia in 2019. After taking power in 2020, he transformed Arenztopia into a prosperous nation. Many roads and monuments are named after him, as he is the first president. He also has a notoriously comprehensive knowledge of Greek Mythology and a degree in classics from the University of Arenztopia. He has a strong amount of influence on many things from science and tech to travel and food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Y.</title>
      <link>/people/tony-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tony-y/</guid>
      <description>Tony Yuan is the Vice President of Arenztopia. He designed the geographical layout of Arenztopia and also the flag. Tony assisted the president greatly during the COVID-19 Pandemic, and created this website and more during the pandemic. He served as Vice President from Arenztopia&#39;s creation until March 2020, when he was impeached for making deals with Milestopia. Kassie K. took over for him. He then won in the 2020-2021 elections and is now the Vice President again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassie K.</title>
      <link>/people/kassie-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/kassie-k/</guid>
      <description>Kassie K. is the Head Judge of Arenztopia. She formerly served as vice president; She succeded Tony Y. in March 2020 and served until December 2021, when she was succeded again by Tony Y. Along with Sam K., she is the leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, specializing in Super Smash Bros Ultimate. Her real name is Kassandra. She was also a very infulential figure in early Arenztopian politics: She was the second person to join modern Arenztopia and helped to create many things at the start including the Arenzese sign language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire P.</title>
      <link>/people/claire-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/claire-p/</guid>
      <description>Claire P. is the Cheif Advisor to the president of Arenztopia. She is one of the 3 original founders of Arenztopia along with Renzo and Kassie. She is an influential figure in Arenztopian politics and has served for two terms as Advisor, and is now serving her third term. She is also the founder of Dripping Cone, the largest ice cream company in the world and the largest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James O.</title>
      <link>/people/james-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/james-o/</guid>
      <description>James O. is a pilot for Arenztopia Airways. He holds the distinction of being the only pilot in the airline to design his own plane. He is also a popular and influential senator in Arenztopia. He&#39;s also a strong advocate of the Arenztopian Military and was the supreme lieutenant commander of the Royal Armed Forces of Arenztopia during the War of Chickentopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livia M.</title>
      <link>/people/livia-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/livia-m/</guid>
      <description>Livia M. is a prolific entreprenuer and runs a chocolate-manufacturing empire. She is the cheif chocolate supplier for Dripping Cone, the biggest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam K</title>
      <link>/people/sam-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sam-k/</guid>
      <description>Sam K. is a leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, along with Kassie K. He specializes in Super Mario Maker, Super Smash Bros, Super Smash Bros Ultimate, and the Pokémon trading card game. In fact, he owns a large Pokémon buiseness that operates multiple stores across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte H.</title>
      <link>/people/charlotte-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/charlotte-h/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte recently won her second term as senator and also a taste tester for Dripping Cone ice cream company, which was voted &amp;ldquo;Best job in Arenztopia&amp;rdquo; by The Arenztopia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clint L.</title>
      <link>/people/clint-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/clint-l/</guid>
      <description>Clint L. is the manager of TC News and leader of a non-recognized, disputed group of islands off the coast of Arenztopia called Heruka. His country is in a disputed state of war with Arenztopia. The dispute is recognized by Clint and to a certain extent by Lorenzo but is not recognized by any other influential Arenztopians and neither side has taken major military or diplomatic or war-related actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellidy J.</title>
      <link>/people/ellidy-j/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ellidy-j/</guid>
      <description>Ellidy is a student currently studying theater at the University of Arenztopia. She is a distinguished Arenztopian for her contributions to the archives of the Department of Theater. She is believed to be cast in a new AZ movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ishaan P.</title>
      <link>/people/ishaan-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ishaan-p/</guid>
      <description>Ishaan is a student studying archaeology at the University of Arenztopia. He discovered the important hominid called Australopithecus Renzosis, which was the first hominid ever discovered in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suhan L.</title>
      <link>/people/suhan-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/suhan-l/</guid>
      <description>Suhan L. is originally of Chinese heritage. He joined Arenztopia and was the former Prime Minister of Arenztopia until the Prime Minister position was removed. He has promised to become a beneficial citizen of Arenztopia so he was readmitted, but after his readmission he made a series of mistakes. He has now resolved those issues and is a great Secretary of Science &amp;amp; Technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henry P.</title>
      <link>/people/henry-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/henry-p/</guid>
      <description>Henry is an animal expert who specializes in corgys. He has saved over 100,000 animals in Arenztopia as of September 2020 from his goverment funded buisiness &amp;ldquo;Arenztopia Animals&amp;rdquo; featured in Olb City Announcer Issue 7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethan H.</title>
      <link>/people/ethan-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/ethan-h/</guid>
      <description>Ethan H. is the manager of the renowned and huge chain of art stores known as Arenztopia Art Store. He is a prominent citizen, often coming to government meetings, and is the richest person in Austerfield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Citizen!</title>
      <link>/people/become-a-citizen-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/become-a-citizen-yourself/</guid>
      <description>When you apply to become a citizen, you get a free certificate and you can do many other things including come to meetings, vote, and order Arenztopia merchandise. To become a citizen, just fill out this form.
Note: Please fill out the Email field with your preferred email, that you or your parents check often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowen F.</title>
      <link>/people/bowen-f/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/bowen-f/</guid>
      <description>Bowen F. is an influential citizen. He is the police chief of the Arenztopia City Police Department (ACPD), and he played an integral part in catching the Woodchuck criminals, crime boss Miles Jordan, and many others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>