<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Arenztopia</title>
    <link>/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Arenztopia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lorenzo A.</title>
      <link>/people/lorenzo-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/lorenzo-a/</guid>
      <description>Lorenzo A. (his full name is not shown for privacy purposes) is the king of Arenztopia. He weilds almost absolute authority. After taking power in 2020, he transformed Arenztopia into a prosperous nation. Many roads and monuments are named after him, as he is the first king. He also has a notoriously comprehensive knowledge of Greek Mythology that he constantly reminds everyone about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassie K.</title>
      <link>/people/kassie-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/kassie-k/</guid>
      <description>Kassie K. is the vice president of Arenztopia. Her real name is Kassandra. She succeded Tony Y. in March 2020. Along with Sam K., she is the leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, specializing in Super Smash Bros Ultimate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tony Y.</title>
      <link>/people/tony-y/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/tony-y/</guid>
      <description>Tony Y. is the chief designer of Arenztopia. He designed virtually everything in Arenztopia, including Arenztopia itself. The flag, capital, and palaces are all of his design. He was also formerly the vice president, and he is on a first-name basis with the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claire P.</title>
      <link>/people/claire-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/claire-p/</guid>
      <description>Claire P. is the Royal Advisor of Arenztopia. She has served on this position for two terms. Claire is also a noted journalist. She is one of the original three people of Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James O.</title>
      <link>/people/james-o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/james-o/</guid>
      <description>James O. is a pilot for Arenztopia Airways. He holds the distinction of being the only pilot in the airline to design his own plane. He is also a popular and influential senator in Arenztopia. He&#39;s also a strong advocate of the Areztopian Military.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livia M.</title>
      <link>/people/livia-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/livia-m/</guid>
      <description>Livia M. is a prolific entreprenuer and runs a chocolate-manufacturing empire. She is the cheif chocolate supplier for Dripping Cone, the biggest company in Arenztopia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam K</title>
      <link>/people/sam-k/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/sam-k/</guid>
      <description>Sam K. is a leading expert in video games in Arenztopia, along with Kassie K. He specializes in Super Mario Maker, Super Smash Bros, Super Smash Bros Ultimate, and the Pokémon trading card game. In fact, he owns a large Pokémon buiseness that operates multiple stores across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte H.</title>
      <link>/people/charlotte-h/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/charlotte-h/</guid>
      <description>Charlotte is a senator and also a taste tester for Dripping Cone ice cream company, which was voted &amp;ldquo;Best job in Arenztopia&amp;rdquo; by The Arenztopia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clint L.</title>
      <link>/people/clint-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/clint-l/</guid>
      <description>Clint L. is the manager of TC News and leader of a non-recognized, disputed group of islands off the coast of Arenztopia called . His country is in a disputed state of war with Arenztopia. The dispute is recognized by Clint and to a certain extent by Lorenzo but is not recognized by any other influential Arenztopians and neither side has taken major military or diplomatic or war-related actions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>